[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
ARCADE
BEFORE GERALD CHEN DISAPPEARED
The professor's premise is a bit flawed.
I organized those ideas into the report.
How is it on your end?
Okay.
SPECIAL OFFER ON TOKENS, 404
I'll send it to you by 10:00 a.m. tomorrow.
That's all for now.
I left my laptop's power cord.
I'm going back to campus.
Don't move.
Or I'll stab you.
Stabbing from this angle?
Even my grandma can do it. Why would we need you?
Watch your back, not just what's ahead.
You need more training.
I only relaxed after hearing Ben's voice.
Let's try again.
Again? I'll need to make a will first.
Why did you make such a mess in here?
Also, you disappeared for three to four months straight.
Couldn't you reply?
You still keep this on you?
Who says that?
I just haven't tossed it.
Take it back.
Mina…
you were too careless just now.
You must always have a plan B.
Got it?
Got it.
Also…
Happy birthday.
Wishing you boundless health and good luck
-Happy birthday -You know I don't celebrate.
Stop singing. It's embarrassing.
Then make a wish.
I don't want to. Wishes are lies.
You child.
How are you so pessimistic?
Come on, make a wish.
Be good.
THE FIXERS
TIEN-BU-LA
Don't get in the car!
Aren't you…
Didn't you see
how William died?
You know so much about him.
Do you think you can get away?
Why are you looking into Zoe's death?
Anyone connected to Zoe will end up like William.
Do you believe he killed himself?
I don't know.
If you want to live,
tell us everything you know.
All I know is that Zoe left the company
because she found out
William secretly invested Yuan Tao's funds in Tolita for fraud.
Was her death related to William?
When William found out, he panicked.
He didn't seem to be acting.
Zoe's husband, Hsu Ming-yi, died a week before Zoe.
You know that, right?
The day Hsu Ming-yi died, he had called William.
And?
William seemed nervous when he answered the phone.
I only heard him say,
"Where did you hear that?"
"They aren't to be messed with."
But before he could finish, the call ended.
I knew it.
He learned something and was silenced.
Have you ever seen this person?
No.
After Zoe died,
did William do anything strange?
Hey, you had better think carefully.
What haven't you told us?
William did ask me to handle some dirty money.
Why do you find that strange?
He wanted me to store the money in a sound wallet.
We never handled cash that way.
A sound wallet?
Who was it for?
I don't know. He told me not to ask.
That's really all I know.
When you get to the airport, don't contact anyone.
Take the first flight out.
Do you hear me?
Could the person William said not to mess with
and the owner of the sound wallet
be the same person?
Hey, what is this sound wallet thingy?
Crypto users have 256-bit private keys,
often managed with mnemonic phrases.
But they can be easily lost on paper
or stolen by hackers from computers.
One way is to convert the password into a 30-second audio file.
Decode it with software, and you can access the account.
If we pursue this lead,
we can trace the money and go from there.
Seek and ye shall find,
but beware of fake signs.
But now William is dead,
and we don't know where the sound wallet is.
I say, why do the rich like to complicate things
and use this weird wallet?
Only cold cash you can see is safe.
Right?
Mina,
did you say Gerald gave you your necklace?
Why do you need this audio file?
It's better if you don't know.
Not again.
You still owe me a meal from last time.
Hey, Taro!
Don't go there.
You'll hit someone.
Does he come here daily?
Today is a holiday. The kindergarten is closed.
He has to burn off energy. How else will he sleep?
Can't you just buy him an iPad?
Screen time can cause myopia, sir.
Shall we take a break? I'll buy you ice cream.
Ice cream has trans fats. You shouldn't eat it.
Hey, Gerald does have a crypto account.
That's about 100 million NTD.
One hundred million?
Holy shit.
He left you so much money?
Gerald wouldn't just leave money.
He must have left other clues.
I traced Gerald's crypto account.
There was a huge transfer just before he went missing.
He bought a house in the mountains.
I'll send you the address when I find it.
Bought a house?
Could he be hiding there?
I'll go with you tomorrow.
Who says I'm going?
Maybe he is just
trying not to get you involved.
Gerald and Ben
have always been protective of me.
But they don't take good care of themselves.
So you think he is still alive, right?
We'll know when we find him tomorrow.
Have some.
It's getting cold.
Why the radishes and meatballs?
They aren't just for you.
Why does anyone want to eat that?
Do you want to try some deep-fried tofu?
No, the skin is gross.
You're so difficult. Try it.
Fine, I'll eat it.
That was a radish, wasn't it?
-It's tofu. -Liar. Show me.
-I didn't see it. -I ate it.
No way. Have one more.
-I just ate one. -You clearly ate a radish.
Try some blood pudding.
-You'll have a meatball after. -Try this.
Have a pork…
Okay, I'll have a pork meatball. Look.
You clearly ate tofu.
Why did Gerald leave Mina so much money?
What is their relationship?
AUTHENTIC TIEN-BU-LA
Mina.
She caught us finishing up a job.
I was going to kill her.
But Gerald saved her.
So she's stuck around ever since?
Doesn't she have family?
She ran away from home.
I never saw a child her age who was so--
-Difficult. -Stubborn.
St…
Stubborn. She wasn't afraid of anything,
as if she had seen the worst of it.
So that's how she became who she is?
Now I get it.
Got it.
But since meeting you guys, she has become more talkative.
Has she?
So you believe Gerald isn't dead?
In our line of work,
how many of us actually make it to retirement?
If I hadn't lost this leg,
I might have died long ago.
What happened to your leg?
A failed mission.
Yeh Yueh Tong saw me as useless,
so they let me go.
So cruel?
Fucking hell.
Hey, here's what.
When I retire, I'll open a stall like you.
I'll sell swamp eel noodles right next to you.
A one-stop shop. It'll profit. Sound good?
Leave me out of it. I don't like crowds.
If you do open a stall, stay away.
Aren't you glad I'm keeping you company?
I'm worried you will feel lonely and cold.
You don't get it.
Have your soup.
I had enough.
-Have some tofu. -Enough.
I'm home.
You're back?
You're still awake? Perfect. Here.
Where is Howie?
Studying in his room.
I got you a snack, tien-bu-la. There's blood pudding, your favorite.
Howie,
your dad bought you a late-night snack. Come over and eat.
Hey, hold on.
What is in that bag?
Goldie said I needed more clothes and bought me some.
Your boss treats you really well.
So handsome and generous.
Invite him over for dinner more often.
Sure.
What's going on? Why are you hiding in your room?
I'm about to take a shower.
-You act all sneaky. What are you up to? -Come on.
Seriously.
You look happy.
Do you remember what your dad got me for my last birthday?
That. A fill light for live streaming.
Yes. And he added, well,
"With the light done right,
Wendy glows so fairylike."
It sucked.
He's like that every time.
Let me tell you.
Your dad
finally figured it out this year.
Madam Fan.
They found Gerald.
Don't alert them.
Send a fixer to keep an eye on them.
If anything happens, report back.
Okay.
As long as he's alive,
we can't give our client an answer.
You know what to do.
No loose ends.
Yeh Yueh Tong doesn't need any more trouble.
Okay.
-Where are you? -I've got things to do at home.
I won't be joining you to be the third wheel today.
Trying to slack off?
The crisp autumn air is perfect for an outing.
Seize your chance, okay? Bye.
Hey.
When you get to the US, if you need money, just ask.
I heard that things are crazy expensive there.
Don't struggle out of pride.
Don't worry. You gave me more than enough to spend.
And I applied for an on-campus job.
I'll make sure to repay you.
This is what I owed your dad anyway.
Felix,
you've got it wrong.
You've been taking care of me all these years.
You paid for it all when my mom was sick.
We owe you.
Stop worrying about money. Your studies matter most.
I'll take you to the airport tomorrow morning.
No need. I've booked a ride.
This is for you, on behalf of your dad.
Your dad's greatest wish was
to send you abroad to study
and see the world for him.
Now you're fulfilling it.
Put it on for me.
Okay, come on.
From now on,
whenever you wear it,
it will feel like…
It will feel like your dad is with you.
Okay, done.
I will come visit you.
Take good care of yourself.
Don't cry, or you'll look uglier than your dad.
Why are you always like this at these moments?
You're annoying.
I… I'm going to pee.
Weirdo.
Why are you stepping down so suddenly?
Do you have a successor in mind?
I'm old and useless.
It's time to step down, so I will.
The exit is still here.
It's easy to back out.
By the time it is removed,
you will be battered no matter how you leave.
Fixer Terra,
that door is heavy.
It will take many people
to remove it.
Indeed, many people want to do that.
Like father, like daughter.
Those who support her, an outsider,
outnumber those who support you, an insider.
I'm old, so I won't meddle anymore.
Old friend,
I hope you can leave on a high note.
I'll be waiting to have tea with you.
THE TIMES ARE AGAINST ME. WHAT CAN I DO?
Excuse me.
Could you interpret this fortune slip?
"Your path to fame is not yet clear."
"With stormy clashes drawing near."
"Guard both sides from loss and pain."
"Step back, sigh not, and wait again."
Are you asking about your family or career?
Madam Fan got this for you.
Hello?
Go up this path, and we'll be there.
LIEN HSIN BRIDGE
His goal is probably the same as ours.
He's a fixer at Yeh Yueh Tong.
Madam Fan knows we've found Gerald.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
Have you seen this person?
Thank you.
All branches have been notified of the time of the secret meeting.
God just offered guidance.
I drew stick number 28.
"The golden days of old have nearly gone."
"A tiger once mighty, now stranded and drawn."
"Fortune is fickle, fey, and fleet."
"So seize the hour before it flees."
Do you remember the stories behind this verse?
One is Cao Cao's capture by Zhang Xiu in Wancheng.
The other is Xiang Yu's defeat.
Surrounded by enemies, he slit his own throat at the Wu River.
One was betrayed,
but ultimately managed to escape danger
and fulfill his ambition.
The other was a dispirited hero
who reached the end of the line.
In your opinion,
which one
is the fortune slip referring to?
This depends on
whether the person can adapt to the situation
and swallow his pride to survive.
You're right.
Is there anything else you need me for?
No.
You have worked hard for Ching He lately.
Take a few days off to rest.
You asked Fixer Gold to help find Gerald.
Aren't you afraid of the fallout
when he learns the truth?
If it's something he must know,
someone is bound to tell him.
I only fear that this move was too hasty.
Certain things, once known,
cannot be unknown.
Someone looks after the potted plants out front.
We should be able to catch them.
Zoe.
Who are you guys?
Stay back.
Put the gun down.
Don't hurt the child.
Back off!
You guys…
Why won't you let me go?
We won't hurt you.
I'm here for Gerald Chen.
He disappeared over a year ago.
He left me clues
to find this place.
You're the one in the photo.
What is your relationship
with Gerald?
He came to kill me.
Are you here?
I'm not coming.
Don't contact me again.
Hello? William.
Hello?
But he couldn't make himself do it when he saw that I was pregnant.
Gerald didn't complete his mission.
Yeh Yueh Tong wouldn't have spared him, and you shouldn't still be here.
That's why he faked my death.
We fooled everyone.
Target Zoe
confirmed dead.
Why are you helping me so much?
I don't want to mess up again.
He put me here to lie low.
So where is he?
GERALD CHEN
-Hello? -I don't think I can make it.
There's a bag of cash in the ceiling.
It should be enough for you and your daughter.
Once things calm down, I--
Hello?
I haven't heard from him since that day.
He might be dead.
Impossible.
He must have planned everything beforehand.
When he was sent to kill me,
he already knew he might die.
What do you mean?
Before his mission, Gerald must have expected
that Yeh Yueh Tong would eliminate him to keep it a secret.
Why did Yeh Yueh Tong want to kill you?
What is this secret that so many people had to die for?
It's you, the Hsuehs.
What do you mean?
The Hsueh family
killed my husband
and came after my daughter and me.
If it weren't for my daughter,
I would have taken you all down with me.
-Why do the Hsuehs-- -Stay back!
Anyhow, a life for a life.
It's only fair.
Calm down.
I just want to know why the Hsuehs want to kill William
and your husband.
Do you really not know, or are you playing dumb?
The Hsin Nan redevelopment project was massive, but approved quickly.
You think the Hsuehs had no hand in it?
William laundered a huge sum of money for them.
How could you not have known?
I just want my daughter and me to be safe.
Just pretend that I'm dead.
I won't say anything.
Don't worry.
We won't tell anyone.
Happy birthday to you
Okay, blow out the candles. Come on.
Mom, happy birthday.
My good son!
Thank you.
You have a good husband too, okay?
MOM
Perfume?
Yes. Hey, do you remember?
We went shopping at a mall when you were pregnant with Howie.
You saw this perfume and really liked it,
but didn't want to splurge on it.
Here, look.
Felix.
There are no secrets in marriage, right?
Are you hiding something from me?
What could I be hiding from you?
Stop imagining things. Go to sleep, okay? Come on.
Are you sure?
I'm sure!
You're being weird.
The brat didn't tell her, did he?
What did you say?
Nothing.
Just sleep. Stop overthinking.
Be good. Go to sleep. Come on.
Based on the exam results,
Mr. Hsueh's liver cancer has metastasized.
We need to start treatment as soon as possible.
Okay, I understand.
Doctor,
this must remain confidential.
Okay.
My illness
might be helpful to you.
Announce it to the public
at the right time.
We're at a critical moment.
There's no room for error.
Got it?
Also,
don't tell your brother yet.
Okay.
Dad,
get some rest.
Things have changed.
I always thought that
as long as Ben and I kept searching…
that meant he was still alive.
He left you the necklace.
Maybe he had hoped that one day you'd see him in that house.
He knew he was going to die.
That's why he left me the necklace
before going on his mission.
It's just that he never thought you'd join Yeh Yueh Tong.
What will you do now?
Madam Fan has kept me around for so long
just to find out Gerald's whereabouts.
What?
Zoe is still alive.
This isn't just bad for Yeh Yueh Tong.
It's also a threat
to the Hsueh family.
I won't harm her.
I know you won't.
At least not now.
What do you mean?
Who knows if you will bring Zoe home
to score points?
You've been using me to find Zoe from the start.
Right?
Ching He is having a secret meeting today.
All six chairpersons will attend.
I'm sure it will be a good show.
TERRA
Fixer Terra isn't one to be late.
What is going on today?
EARTH
Oh.
Wait.
One will be missing.
Folks.
Chairman.
Fixer Terra is not coming.
He was found
dead in the suburbs.
How could this be?
We will pause our discussion for today
until I figure out what happened to Fixer Terra.
Chairman,
we should carefully discuss
whether there are better candidates
for the position of Fixer Celestial.
What do you mean by that?
The Hong family has served Ching He for generations.
Everything we do
is in Ching He's best interests.
It has stood strong for over a century
thanks to
leaders who adapted to change
and made the right choices.
Sir Hong has agreed
to hand over the key to the Kuang Ming Chamber.
But Thackery won't step down so easily.
After an incident this serious,
as chairman,
it is my ultimate responsibility to find out why.
I have a way to deal with Thackery.
Please do tell.
You will know when the time comes.
Madam Fan,
to our great partnership.
LULLABY
This will save your life.
If you're ever in danger,
use this to contact Ching He.
CHING HE TEMPLE
Hello?
Gerald Chen said
that if my life was ever in danger,
I should make this call.
Subtitle translation by: Hannah Liu